We can also add up a prompt over here in order to change the very image that it created
for us, and in order to make it better and make it closer to what we were looking for.
But another thing that we can do is that we can come here and click on download image
over here, as you see.
So this is also doable.
And what else?
We can share this image, and that's pretty much all that we have.
So we can also add up a, let's say, thread-like prompt ink.
So we can come here.
And if this image has problems, has specific problems, for example, I don't want the
text to be over here, or I don't want the logo to be over here.
Or for example, I want it to be more crowded, right?
Or I want to change a very specific thing about this image.
What I can do is that I can click on it and add my changes over here, as you see.
So this has changed the image and style to, yes.
So this is continuous prompting on a single generation.